http://www.nationalreaderboard.com/pages/nrs-policies

We recommend Sign Companies call to place your order @ 800.243.6676
Our Best Selling Gemini Pronto Brand
No Minimum Order Durable Rigid Letters for Push Up-Drop Down Tracking Individual or Sets Available
Shop
Flexible letters
Economical Full Letters Sets
Made for Roadside Signs ONLY Use with Flexible "Texas Tracking" Easily Bent in Hand Sizes: 4", 6", 8" Only Available in Full Sets
Shop
Slotted Sign Letters
Unique 3 Dimensional Letters
Slotted Back Hooks onto tracking Wide Stroked Flat Matte Finish Sizes: 6", 8", 10" in Black and Red Individual Letters Only
Giant Price Points
Specialty panels that are twice the size of your regular letters
Letter Changer Poles
Don't use a ladder to change your message.
Changeable letter poles with adjustable heights and cup sizes to make updating your message fast and simple.
Shop
Letter Pole Suction Cups and Replacement Parts
Change your suction cup frequently.
If your current letter pole suction cup is cracked, warped or rotted, it won't hold your letters securely and you risk dropping them.
Shop
Letter Storage Cabinets
Keep your changeable sign letters safe.
Each letter cabinet alphabetizes up to 300 sign letters, minimizes scratching and breakage and best of all, you'll never have to dig around for hours in an old cardboard box.
Shop
Readerboard Tracking and Rivets
Keeping up your readerboard sign is easy.
We carry the tracking and rivets you need to keep your marquee sign in shape for years to come.
Shop
Graphics
Sign Repair
Get Educated
How To Videos
Installing Letters, Caring for your Readerboard, and Using a Letter Pole are a Snap if You Know How to do it Right
Learn More
Downloadable Tools
Get the Answers You Need Fast so You Can Get back to Working on What matters most, Your Business
Learn More
Contact
Home
›
NRS Policies
NRS Policies
Returns
National Readerboard Supply wants to ensure that each customer is able to utilize their sign to its maximum potential. We understand that occasionally what you have ordered may not fit your needs, and we will attempt to provide you with the correct product.
Material may not be returned without prior authorization. Call our customer service team, 800-243-6676, for a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) number. Unauthorized returns will not be accepted or refunded.
Returns, when authorized, must be made within 30 days of receipt of order, freight prepaid and utilizing a tracking number.
To be eligible for a refund, your item must be returned unused and in the same condition that you received it.
Be sure to tightly wrap the items (shrink wrap is highly recommended for letters) so the product does NOT move and get damaged while in transit. Damaged or scratched items cannot be refunded.
Returned merchandise, when accepted, is subject to a 15% restocking fee.
Used, damaged, or custom manufactured items cannot be returned under any condition.
Damaged shipments – orders received damaged MUST be processed for claim within 10 days of receipt of shipment.
Claims received after this time period will not be processed. Call our customer service team to place the claim.
Refunds
Refunds will be credited to the original purchasing method. Please allow 14-21 days of processing time. If after this time you have not received a refund, please contact us at sales@nationalreaderboard.com to verify we have received and processed your return.
Shipping
To return your product, you should mail your product to:
National Readerboard Supply ATTN: Returns2305 Old Callahan DriveKnoxville, TN 37912
Shipping costs are non-refundable. You will be responsible for paying shipping costs to return your item. The only exception is if you were sent an item you did not order. In those cases, a call-tag will be issued and shipping paid for.
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways. Some examples are when you:
Make an online, over the phone, or faxed, purchase from us
Request customer service or contact us
Submit a testimonial
Participate in a contest, sweepstake, promotion, or survey; or otherwise submit personal information to us.
Personal information is information that identifies you specifically. The personal information we collect may include contact and payment information like your name, email and physical addresses, phone numbers, and credit and debit card numbers. When you ask us to ship an order, we may collect information you provide us such as the name, address, and phone number of recipients.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We are compliant under PCI Data Security Standards.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your online account, calling us or sending us an email. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
